epscu.com 2002-04-08

# Privacy

Payment Systems for Credit Unions, Inc. (PSCU) is one of the largest 24x7 call centers and transaction card service providers for credit unions in the U.S. In addition, PSCU is the largest credit union service organization (CUSO) in the nation. PSCU is a cooperative organization dedicated to promoting the success of our members by delivering financial services, technology through its ePSCU division, and operational support exclusively for credit unions.

PSCU and ePSCU intend for pscu.net and epscu.com to complement the services that each organization respectively provides. Collectively PSCU and ePSCU believe that online security and privacy are important to the future success of the Internet and electronic commerce. We also believe that online security and privacy are important to our member credit unions and to their members as well.

PSCU and ePSCU have a strong commitment to the issues of trust and privacy on the World Wide Web as demonstrated by our agreement with ICSA.net, the worldwide leader in Internet security assurance services, to provide TruSecure™ certification for PSCU's security policies and technical internetworking infrastructure.

We are committed to guarding your data, protecting your members' privacy, and developing technology that gives consumers the most powerful, safe, online experience available anywhere.

After all, isn't that what you expect from us?

**Privacy**   
PSCU defines "Privacy" as the measures in place to ensure that any information provided to us is maintained in strict confidence and not distributed, shared, or otherwise used without the expressed permission of the information provider.

Should you merely visit either site, pscu.net or epscu.com, we do not collect any personal information about you. Should you decide you would like additional information about PSCU or ePSCU, you will be asked to register online. During registration the information disclosed is retained, such as your name and email address. 

We also request and retain during registration other demographic information such as address, credit union affiliation and purpose for your visit. We use demographic information in the aggregate only for statistical analysis and internal research purposes to help us understand who is using our site and become better equipped to serve your needs. **Neither PSCU nor ePSCU sells, distributes or discloses your personally identifiable information collected at registration to any third parties.**

Our website may contain links to other websites. Accordingly, neither PSCU nor ePSCU can be responsible for the privacy practices or the content of the linked websites and encourages you to read the privacy statement of any linked websites to become acquainted with their specific privacy practices.

ePSCU's _InfoLink_ site for credit card data currently accepts user ID, password, credit card account number(s), and zip code(s). Future versions of this site may accept other types of information (SSN, mother's maiden name, birthdate, e-mail addresses, etc.) that allow the site to verify the credit union members' access privileges.

Any information credit union members provide to register or use any of ePSCU Internet product sites will be used only as required to enable the members' registration or use of the sites. The information members provide is stored in ePSCU data center computers in a secure environment. Any e-mail addresses that credit union members provide or will provide on the site are for supporting communication between the credit union member and ePSCU's call center representatives.

**_ePSCU does not share any user-provided information with outside parties._**

**Collection, Use, and Disclosure**

_**Cookies**_   
PSCU and ePSCU avoid the use of cookies whenever possible but cannot guarantee that we will not use them. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on the PSCU or ePSCU sites. Once the user closes the browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on either the PSCU or ePSCU site, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on either site. If you reject the cookie, you may still use either site, but the site's general inability to verify you as the user may result in your inability to participate in any bulletin boards, sweepstakes, contests or drawings either site might sponsor or promote. Cookies also enable a site to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on each site. Also, please understand that some business partners of PSCU or ePSCU may use cookies on their respective sites. However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

_**IP Addresses**_   
PSCU and ePSCU use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

_**Demographic Information**_   
PSCU and ePSCU will share aggregated demographic information with their partners. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. These statistics help PSCU / ePSCU evaluate the effectiveness and appeal of various services and segments of our site.
